accuradio.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy / Privacy Policy / Knowledge Base - AccuRadio Support

AccuRadio.com and its affiliate sites receive information from and about you in three ways: (I) information you provide to us directly, (II) inform we automatically receive from devices you use to access AccuRadio's service, and (III) information we automatically receive from third parties. AccuRadio makes every effort to ensure that the information we collect about you cannot be used to identify you personally, nor can it be used to spam or target you for viruses or other types of malware.

(I) When you register with AccuRadio, you must provide certain information such as your email address, year of birth, gender and zip code in addition to creating a password. By registering with us you automatically subscribe to occasional AccuRadio newsletters announcing new features, channels, and promotions. You may unsubscribe from receiving newsletters at any time by clicking the "Unsubscribe" button appearing at the bottom of the newsletter and then following the instructions provided. AccuRadio also receives information about you whenever you email us, participate in a poll or survey, or respond to an advertisement appearing on our service. Finally, AccuRadio uses cookies and beacons to collect certain information. Cookies are used to save information like your artist deselects and song ratings, and beacons may be placed in emails and on webpages to let us know which emails recipients have opened and how many unique visitors have visited a webpage.

(II) When you access the AccuRadio service our servers receive and record certain information about the type of the device you used such as a computer, tablet, mobile phone, automobile, etc., and we may also collect other information such as the applicable operating system version and type, unique identifiers like android ID, IDFA, MAC address or VIN, as well as carrier or other transactional information for the device.

(III) AccuRadio sometimes receives non-personal information about you from third parties like advertisers and service partners and this information is stored on our servers. This information generally includes how often you have viewed their ads or whether you have clicked through an ad.

Any of the three types of information discussed above cannot be used to identify you personally, but we may use certain non-personally identifiable information to improve the design or content of our site. We also use non-personally identifiable information to analyze site usage to be shared with our advertisers and clients for the sole purpose of better targeting ads to our listeners. We also may be required, in certain limited circumstances, to provide certain information to comply with the law or legal process or in the event of a corporate reorganization, merger or sale of AccuRadio or any of its affiliates.

Finally, we will often link to sites whose privacy policies differ from ours. You should consult other sites' privacy policies as we have no control over information that is submitted to or collected by these outside sites, nor can AccuRadio, its affiliates or employees assume any liability whatsoever in the event that any outside site collects, uses or shares any information about you in violation of its own privacy policy.

If you have any questions or concerns about the AccuRadio privacy policy for this site or any of its implementations, you may contact us using our [feedback system](http://help.accuradio.com/).
